{
    "quiz": {
        "ObjectiveC": [
                       {"question":"Indica TATA", "answer":"Four Doors India Ford Times"},
                       {"question":"What is Core Data?", "answer":"Six Doors"},
                       {"question":"Imran",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Rijwan",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Salman",  "answer":"Harbaspur UP"},
                       {"question":"Maxima", "answer":"Six Doors"},
                       {"question":"Imran",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Rijwan",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Salman",  "answer":"Harbaspur UP"},
                       {"question":"Maxima", "answer":"Six Doors"},
                       {"question":"Imran",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Rijwan",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Salman",  "answer":"Harbaspur UP"},
                       {"question":"Rahil Ali",  "answer":"Jahanbad UP"}
                       ]
        
    }
}
